(Bernadette:)I can hook you up with anxiety
medication, antidepressants.
(Penny:)Really.
(Stuart:)Do you have any of these?
(Amy:)Hello, Mr. Rat Brain.
(Amy:)Not so bitey without the rest of the
rat to back us up now, are we?
(Howard:)-Anybody home?
(Amy:)Hey, what brings you guys here?
(Raj:)Well, we were just on our way
to lunch and wanted to see
(Raj:)-if you'd like to join.
-Why?
(Amy:)Because Sheldon's
not here this week,
(Amy:)and you don't think I
have any other options?
(Amy:)I'm just kidding.
I'll get my purse.
(Bert:)Hi, Amy. I... Oh.
(Bert:)I'm sorry. I didn't know
you had any company.
(Amy:)That's okay.
Bert, this is Howard and Rajesh.
(Amy:)Guys, this is Bert.
(Raj:)-Hey. Good to see you.
-Hey.
(Bert:)Anyway, I wanted to show you
(Bert:)this tourmalinated quartz
that we got in the lab.
(Amy:)This is so pretty.
(Amy:)Bert works for the
geology department.
Yeah. You know what geologists
and Bon Jovi have in common?
(Howard:)You're both into rock?